So now my time is up
現在我時間到了
Your game starts my heart moving?
換你開始遊戲 我心將動搖?
Past time has no meaning for us it's not enough!
過去的時間對我們毫無意義 這樣還遠遠不夠!
Will we make it better or just stand here longer
我們是否能做得更好 還是繼續停留原地
Say it we can't end here till we can get it enough!!
說吧 「我們不能在這結束 要直到滿意才罷休!!」
絶対的根拠はウソうそだらけ
絕對的根源滿是謊言
いつだってあるのは 僕の
無論何時都存在於我的是
自信や不安をかき混ぜた
自信與不安混雜
弱いようで 強い僕!!
看似軟弱卻強勁的我!!
This is my own judgment!! Got nothing to say!!
這就是我的判斷!! 沒什麼好說的!!
もしも他に何か思いつきゃ 速攻言うさ!!
其他若有什麼異議 就快快道來
「 完全感覚 Dreamerが僕の名さ!」
「完全感覺Dreamer就是我的名號!」
Well say it ? well say it!!
吶 不說嗎? 吶 就說吧!!
あればあるで聞くが今は Hold on!
聽得越清楚此刻就越能堅持!
Yeah when I'm caught in fire
沒錯 當我身陷烈焰之中
When I rise up higher
我將向更高處邁進
Do you see me out there
你是否能目送著我
waiting for the next chance we get
直到我們捉住下個機會
Will we make it IT'S NOT ENOUGH!!
我們是否能做得更好 會是仍不滿足!!
or just stand here longer
還是繼續停留原地
Say it we can't end here till we can get it enough!!
說吧「我們不能在這結束，要直到滿意才罷休!!」
確信犯? 知能犯? NO NO NO!!
いつだってその 場しのぎの
無論何時都必須忍受
持論や理論を織り交ぜた
主見與理論編織交錯
自由さユニークさもなく
自由與獨特皆為空談
This is my own judgment!!
這就是我的判斷!!
Got nothing to say!!
沒什麼好說的!!
もしも他に何か思いつきゃ  速攻言うさ!!
其他若有什麼異議 就快快道來
「 完全感覚 Dreamerが僕の名さ！」
「完全感覺Dreamer就是我的名號！」
Well say it ? well say it!!
吶 不說嗎? 吶 就說吧!!
You know I've got to be NUMBER ONE!!
你知道我必須成為第一吧!!
どうだい? 予想外?
怎麼樣? 預料外?
面食らって はばかれて
困惑著 忌憚著
後退?して撤退?
後退? 然後撤退?
ってYeah
恩? Yeah
完全感覺Dreamer的空想!!
誰が何を言おうが言わまいが無関係!!
無論被誰說了什麼都無所謂!!
どうやったっていつも変わらない
無論怎樣都不會改變
壁を闇をこれからぶっ壊していくさ!!
阻擋的高牆和黑暗都將被擊破!!
完全感覺 Dreamer
When I'm caught in fire
當我身陷烈焰之中
When I rise up higher
我將向更高處邁進
Do you see me out there
你能看著我到最後嗎
I can't get enough! Can't get enough!!
我不會就此滿足! 無法滿足!!